<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<index version="1" commit="3a04f4ae5581055040033ba9e2e09f996dc95433">
  <category name="NextVariation">
    <reapack name="NextVariation.lua" type="script" desc="Next Variation">
      <metadata>
        <description><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\deff0{\fonttbl{\f0 \fswiss Helvetica;}{\f1 Courier;}}
{\colortbl;\red255\green0\blue0;\red0\green0\blue255;}
\widowctrl\hyphauto

{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs36 Next Variation\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Sets content of selected audio item to next variation found. Perfect for sound designers working with recordings containing multiple variations in single file. Uses built-in transient detection, which can be configured action "Transient detection sensitivity/threshold: Adjust..."\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Usage:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa0 \li360 \fi-360 \bullet \tx360\tab Add audio file containing multiple sounds into timeline\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa0 \li360 \fi-360 \bullet \tx360\tab Trim first sound variation from the audio item\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa0 \li360 \fi-360 \bullet \tx360\tab Select audio item and run the script\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa0 \li360 \fi-360 \bullet \tx360\tab It should now contain the second variation in audio file\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa0 \li360 \fi-360 \bullet \tx360\tab If results are not satisfactory configure the transient detection through action "Transient detection sensitivity/threshold: Adjust..."\sa180\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Features:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa0 \li360 \fi-360 \bullet \tx360\tab Supports multiple selected items\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa0 \li360 \fi-360 \bullet \tx360\tab Uses separate tracks for item manipulation, so shouldn't mess with unselected track content\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa0 \li360 \fi-360 \bullet \tx360\tab Loops through item content, if Loop source is enabled\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa0 \li360 \fi-360 \bullet \tx360\tab Preserves item fade information\sa180\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Known issues and workaround:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa0 \li360 \fi-360 \bullet \tx360\tab Built-in transient detection is not content aware and therefor you often have to choose between getting false positives or not finding the next variation. False positives are not really a big issue, since you can just run the script again (using keyboard shortcut strongly recommended). Sensitivity 35%, Threshold -24db settings seem to work fine (= a bit too false positive happy, but not missing anything) with most audio content.\sa180\par}
}
]]></description>
      </metadata>
      <version name="1.0" author="Sauli Lehtinen / Demoji" time="2022-03-14T11:29:49Z">
        <source main="main">https://github.com/saul-l/REAPER-Bits-and-bobs/raw/798b5a15a818403636e086e89a84e8061d31e1d6/NextVariation/NextVariation.lua</source>
      </version>
      <version name="1.01" author="Demoji / Sauli" time="2022-03-15T12:34:16Z">
        <source main="main">https://github.com/saul-l/REAPER-Bits-and-bobs/raw/b426d1743618c462a5d3e692ca28245964d954d6/NextVariation/NextVariation.lua</source>
      </version>
    </reapack>
  </category>
  <metadata>
    <description><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\deff0{\fonttbl{\f0 \fswiss Helvetica;}{\f1 Courier;}}
{\colortbl;\red255\green0\blue0;\red0\green0\blue255;}
\widowctrl\hyphauto

{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs36 Reaper Bits and bobs\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 ReaPack compatible repository for my random REAPER scripts and jsfx\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Currently content:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Next Variation}\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa0 \li360 \fi-360 \bullet \tx360\tab Sound design workflow improvement plugin for automatically moving item audio content start position to next variation.\sa180\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Region Naming Tool}\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa0 \li360 \fi-360 \bullet \tx360\tab Naming tool, which makes it easy to name multiple regions at once and allows using custom word lists\sa180\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Split and Keep Fade Curves}\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa0 \li360 \fi-360 \bullet \tx360\tab Does exactly what name implies. I got tired of split working how I wanted it to work\sa180\par}
}
]]></description>
  </metadata>
</index>
